Klevis Rrapushaj

Full Stack Developer | Computer Science



Personal details

Name

Klevis Rrapushaj

Email address

klevisolutions@gmail.com

Phone number

+355 69 269 4822

Address

Lagja Naftetari, Fier 9301 Fier

Nationality

Albanian

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/klevisrrapushaj

Github

github.com/kleviscoding

Portfolio

klevis-code.web.app

Profile

Passionate programmer with approximately 6 years of experience in software development. Proficient in both frontend and backend development, utilizing a diverse stack of technologies. Excels in JavaScript/TypeScript, React, React Native,Angular, Node.js, Laravel, and Symfony. Experienced in Test-Driven Development (TDD), NoSQL and SQL databases, Git version control, and cloud computing with AWS .Experienced on mobile development also Android and IOS .

Education

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

10/2019 - 07/2022

Albania University, Tirana

Graduated with an A/9 grade, excelling academically.

Conducted internships, participated in coding competitions, and engaged in student organizations.

High School Diploma, Computer Science

09/2015 - 06/2019

Albanian College Durres, Durres

Actively participated in community service, internships, research projects, and extracurricular activities.

Certificates

Computer Programmer/Operator/Systems Engineer

01/2018

Instituti "Harry T. Fultz"

Employment

Full Stack Developer

01/2022 - Present

ICT Solutions · Self-employed, Tirana, Albania (Remote)

- Joined ICT Solution, a company established by a university professor to facilitate independent work for developers.
- Engaged in two contracts with U.S.-based company Paleovalley, working on front-end, back-end, and mobile development.
- Subsequently, joined Fleetpulse, another U.S.-based firm, for a year, with responsibilities encompassing full-stack development and mobile

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruitment for the position to which I am applying.

development.

- Utilized PHP, JavaScript/TypeScript, React, React Native, Flutter, Angular, Laravel, Node.js, and GraphQL.
- Proficient in microservices, Docker, and AWS for implementing various features, including payment APIs, geolocation services, tax calculation, and delivery functionality.

Full Stack Engineer

10/2017 - 12/2021

ArkEvo Group, Tirana, Albania (Hybrid)

- Spent four transformative years at ArkEvo Group, a dynamic software house, with a hybrid work environment.
- Worked on diverse projects spanning transportation, fintech, CMS (WordPress & Shopify), education, health, e-commerce, and local businesses, serving clients in the USA and Europe.
- Developed expertise in JavaScript/TypeScript, PHP, React,React Native Angular, Node.js, Laravel, Symfony, and various architectural design patterns.
- Utilized Scrum and Kanban methodologies for agile project management.
- Proficient in Git, GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket, and deploying applications on cloud platforms like Heroku, AWS, GCP, and Azure.

Software Engineer (Paid Internship)

12/2016 - 08/2017

Kastrati Group, Tirana, Albania (On-site)

- Joined Kastrati Group as a software engineering intern, focusing on developing PaaS solutions and working with React, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Laravel, and Node.js.
- Gained hands-on experience with REST APIs and payment APIs, enriching skills during a 9-month internship also created the company mobile app regarding top ups.

Skills

Web Development	••••••
Mobile Development (Android & IOS)	••••••
JavaScript	••••••
TypeScript	••••••
React	••••••
React Native	••••••

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruitment for the position to which I am applying.

Angular **Flutter** Node.js Laravel **Symfony Test-Driven Development (TDD)** NoSQL and SQL databases Git version control **AWS cloud computing Object-oriented programming (OOP) FP** (short for functional programming) Domain-driven design (DDD) Languages **English**

Hobbies

- Football
- Swimming
- Hiking

Fier, November 2, 2023

KRR

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruitment for the position to which I am applying.